http://www.olivetree.com/press/privacy.php

Olive TreeMenuBible AppsAppsiPad/iPhoneAndroid Tablet/PhoneKindle FireMac OSWindowsDaily Bible MeditationAll AppsBibles & Study BiblesEnglish BiblesAudio BiblesStudy BiblesStrong’s TaggedGreek and HebrewNon-English BiblesAll BiblesBible Study ToolsStudy ToolsStudy BiblesCommentary SetsCommentariesGreek and Hebrew ToolsConcordances & Cross ReferencesDictionariesMaps & AtlasesBiblical StudiesSermonsBiblical History & CultureBible Handbooks & IntroductionsQuick ReferenceDevotionals All Bible Study ToolsDevotional & Christian LivingDevotionalDevotionalsAudio BooksTheologyPrayerApologeticsSpiritual GrowthChristian LivingChurch & PastoralTitles for WomenMarriage & FamilyTitles for MenChristian InspirationChildren & TeenBiographyAll BooksFreeBible AppsBiblesStudy ToolsBooksAll Free BooksSale & FeaturedSaleThis Week's SaleNew ReleasesEnhanced for Bible StudyEnhanced with Reading PlansCollectionsUpcoming ReleasesSign Up for RewardsGift CardsView All DealsAccountYour CartThis Week Only - Save Up to 80% on Select Titles!
Olive Tree Policies
Jump to:
Your privacy is important to us at Olive Tree Bible Software. So we've developed this privacy policy
that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information.
Please take a moment
to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know you have any questions.
Effective Date: September 12, 2020
We at Olive Tree Bible Software respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Notice applies to
personal customer information obtained by our Company, through our Services: web sites, mobile sites,
applications (“apps”), emails, and widgets.
The Notice describes the types of personal information we obtain about customers, how we use the
information, and with whom we share it. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security
of the information and how you can contact us about our privacy practices. Our Services are for a
general audience, are not targeted to children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information
from children under 13 years of age.
Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section:
Information We Obtain
Information Obtained by Automated Means Through Our Services
How We Use the Information We Obtain
Information We Share
Your Choices
Accessing, Reviewing, Updating and Modifying Personal Information
We obtain personal information about customers through our Services, publicly and commercially available
sources, and from some third-party services (such as social media networks). The types of personal
information we may obtain include:
Contact information (such as name, postal address, email address and telephone and/or mobile numbers);
Username and password when you register through our Services;
Geolocation data;
Other information you may provide to us, such as through our “Submit a Request” or “Contact Us” feature; and
Behavioral data such as website pages visited or time spent using our Services.
Information Obtained by Automated Means Through Our Services
We also may obtain certain information through our Services by automated means, such as cookies
(including HTTP, HTML5 and Flash cookies), web beacons, web server logs, JavaScript and similar
technologies, including technologies designed to obtain information regarding your use of our Services.
The information we obtain in this manner may include IP address, mobile device advertising ID, browser
characteristics, device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs,
information on actions taken on our Services, and dates and times you access or use our Services. In
connection with our mobile apps, we also may obtain your phone number and details about your mobile carrier.
A “cookie” is a file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to
uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A “web beacon”
also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies
and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. Through these
automated collection methods, we obtain “clickstream data,” which is a log of the links and other
content on which a visitor clicks while browsing a website. As the visitor clicks through the website,
a record of the action may be collected and stored. We also may use similar automated means to obtain and
store information regarding your actions while using our mobile apps.
We may link certain data elements obtained through automated means, such as your browser or device
information, with other information we have obtained about you to let us know, for example, whether you
have opened an email we sent to you, what search queries you may have run and what advertisements you may
have seen on our Services or on third-party websites and apps. Your browser may tell you how to be
notified when you receive certain types of cookies or how to restrict or disable certain types of
cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of
our Services. Your device settings also may allow you to prohibit mobile app platforms (such as Apple
and Google) from sharing certain information obtained by automated means with us through our apps or
other app developers.
In addition, if you register with us through or connect your account with us to a third-party social
media network (such as Facebook, Google, or Twitter), we may obtain certain information about you from
the relevant social media network, such as your user ID and/or user name associated with that social
media network, the information contained in your public profile on the social media network and friends
lists. The specific information we obtain depends on your privacy settings on the applicable social
media network.
The providers of third-party apps, tools, widgets and plug-ins on our Services, such as social media
sharing tools, also may use automated means to collect information regarding your interactions with
these features. This information is collected directly by the providers of those features and is subject
to the privacy policies or notices of those providers. Our Company is not responsible for those providers’
information practices.
How We Use the Information We Obtain
We may use the information collected from and about you to:
Provide our products and services;
Create and manage online accounts;
Send promotional materials, alerts regarding available offers and other communications, including
communications through the Services and outside of the Services, such as via email and through
third-party websites and apps;
Communicate about, and administer participation in, special events, promotions, programs, offers,
surveys, contests and market research;
Respond to inquiries from you and other third-parties, including inquiries from law enforcement
agencies;
Anonymize personal information to provide third parties with aggregated data reports showing
anonymized information and other non-personal information;
Supplement your personal information collected from you with additional information from publicly
and commercially available sources, and/or information from third-party services;
Associate your browser and/or device with other browsers or devices you use for the purpose of
providing relevant and easier access to content, advertising across browsers and devices, and
other operational/business purposes.
Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing, enhancing, analyzing and
improving our Services; managing our communications; performing data analytics; and performing
accounting, auditing and other internal functions);
Protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other unlawful activity, claims and other
liabilities; and
Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards, contractual
obligations and our policies.
In addition, we and our third-party service providers may use information collected through automated
means including cookies, web beacons, web server logs, JavaScript and similar technologies for purposes
such as (1) customizing our users’ visits to and use of our Services, (2) delivering content (including
advertising) tailored to our users’ interests and the manner in which our users use our Services, and
(3) managing our Services and other aspects of our business.
We may use third-party analytics services on our Services, such as those of Google Analytics. The
analytics providers that administer these services use technologies such as cookies, web beacons, web
server logs and similar technologies to help us analyze your use of the Services. The information
collected through these means may be disclosed to these analytics providers and other relevant third
parties who use the information, for example, to evaluate use of the Services. To learn more about how to
opt out of Google Analytics services, please visit the link below:
Google Analytics:
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
We also may use your personal information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time
of collection.
Information We Share
We may share customer personal information with:
Service providers in the US and other jurisdictions who perform services on our behalf.
Our third party clients or business partners, such as publishers and social media networks, for
marketing purposes, such as targeted promotional emails.
In addition, when the information collected from or about you does not identify you as a specific person,
we may share it with third parties.
We may further disclose information about you (1) if we are required to do so by law or legal process,
(2) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, and (3) when we believe disclosure
is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an
investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity. We also reserve the right to
transfer personal information we have about you in the event of a proposed or completed sale or transfer
of all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or
liquidation).
Your Choices
We offer you certain choices in connection with the personal information we obtain about you, such as how
we communicate with you.
To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our marketing mailing lists or submit a
request, please contact us as outlined in the How To Contact Us Section below.
You also can unsubscribe from our marketing mailing lists by following the “Unsubscribe” link in our emails.
Accessing, Reviewing, Updating and Modifying Personal Information
You have the right to access, review, update, and correct inaccuracies in your personal information in our
custody and control, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. You may request access, updates to
and corrections of inaccuracies in your personal information by emailing or writing to us at the contact
information set out below. We may request certain personal information for the purposes of verifying the
identity of the individual seeking access to his/her personal information records.
Notice to California Residents
If you are a California Resident, please review our California
Privacy Rights Page for information on your privacy rights and for the ability to opt-out of any
future sale of your data. Please note Olive Tree does not at this time sell any personal information.
How We Protect and Retain Personal Information
We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect personal information we
have about you against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access,
disclosure or use.
We make reasonable efforts to ensure a level of security appropriate to the risk of
the processing, taking into account the costs of implementation and nature of the processing of such
personal information.
We retain personal information for the period needed to fulfill the purposes for which the personal
information was collected and as otherwise required or permitted by applicable law, such as in relation to
our record retention obligations.
Transfers of Information
The Services may be hosted in and managed from a country outside the country in which you initially
provided the information, including the United States. We may transfer the personal information we
collect about you to the United States and/or another country, which may not be deemed to have the same
data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When your personal
information is in such countries, it may be accessed by the courts, law enforcement and national security
authorities in accordance with applicable law. If you are a user located outside the United States or the
country to which your information may be transferred, you understand and consent to having any personal
information processed in the United States and/or such country. Your consent includes the use of cookies
and other tracking technologies as described above. When we transfer your information, we will protect
that information as described in this Notice.
Links to Third-Party Sites, Apps and Services
For your convenience and information, our Services may provide links to third-party sites, apps and
services that may be operated by companies not affiliated with Olive Tree Bible Software. These companies
may have their own privacy notices or policies, which we strongly suggest you review. We are not
responsible for the privacy practices of any sites, apps, or services outside our Company.
Updates to Our Privacy Notice
This Privacy Notice may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our
personal information practices. For significant changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice
on our Services indicating at the top of the Notice when it was most recently updated.
How To Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice or the manner in which we or our service
providers treat your personal information, would like to exercise your choices, or would like us to update
information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us as follows:
support@olivetree.com
You also may write to:
At Olive Tree, we want you to feel safe and secure when you provide us with your personal information
online. For this reason we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt your credit card and other
sensitive information when you make product purchases or request technical assistance. The process of
encryption minimizes the possibility of unauthorized individuals from viewing your information as it is
securely transmitted over the Internet. Once received, your credit card information is not transmitted over
the Internet again.
However, even with such protection policies and safeguard procedures in place, there
is always the possibility of fraud occurring. If you believe unauthorized disclosure or use of your credit
information has occurred, please follow the reporting procedures defined by your credit card's issuing
bank and contact us immediately.
Most credit card companies cover all charges that result form unauthorized
use of your credit card or may limit your liability to $50.
EULA
OLIVE TREE END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT
Please read this Olive Tree Bible Software End User License Agreement (EULA) carefully. This EULA is
a contract between you and Olive Tree Bible Software, a division of Gospel Technologies LLC.
(Olive Tree) and governs your use of (i) any Olive Tree software (including but not limited to the
Bible App by Olive Tree products), and (ii) any Olive Tree products and content, including but not
limited to Bible files, e-book files, reference materials, font files, daily reading files, and any other
files available for download or as a boxed product), including any Updates (defined below) and
accompanying printed or electronic documentation (collectively, the Product).
BY CLICKING 'I AGREE' OR DOWNLOADING, INSTALLING, OR USING THE PRODUCT, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS
EULA. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS EULA, DO NOT CLICK 'I AGREE' OR DOWNLOAD, INSTALL OR USE
THE PRODUCT.
1. ACKNOWLEDGEMENT. You and Olive Tree acknowledge that (i) you are licensing the Product from Olive Tree
and not Apple, Google, or the like, and (ii) Apple, Google, nor any other app store vendor, is not a
party to this EULA. As between Apple, Google, or any other app store vendor and Olive Tree, Olive Tree
is solely responsible for the Product, the content therein, any maintenance or support services to the
extent required by applicable law, any warranties to the extent that such warranties have not been
disclaimed, and any claims that you or any other party may have relating to the Product (including for
infringement of third party intellectual property rights and consumer protection and product liability
claims). You and Olive Tree acknowledge and agree that Apple and its subsidiaries are third-party
beneficiaries of this EULA, and that Apple will have the right (and will be deemed to have accepted the
right) to enforce this EULA against you as a third-party beneficiary hereof.
2. LICENSE GRANT. Subject to your compliance with the terms and conditions of this EULA,
Olive Tree grants to you a personal, limited, non-exclusive, non-sublicenseable, non-transferable,
revocable license to install and use one copy of the Product on up to five (5) supported devices
that you own or control.
Other than as specifically permitted during a free trial period, if applicable, you may not manipulate the
Product, Olive Tree's website or other Olive Tree resources to access or utilize any purchase-based or
subscription-based feature of the Product unless you have paid the applicable fee. Olive Tree is not
obligated to provide any such free trial period for any Product.
3. OWNERSHIP; PROPRIETARY MARKS. The Product is protected by copyright and other intellectual property
laws and treaties. Except for the limited license granted to you in Section 2 of this EULA, Olive Tree
reserves all right, title, and interest, including but not limited to copyright, patent, trade secret,
and all other intellectual property and proprietary rights, in and to the Product. You agree that Olive
Tree does not, directly or by implication, by estoppel or otherwise, grant any other rights or licenses
to you under this EULA. You may not delete, obscure or alter any copyright, trademark or other proprietary
rights notices appearing on the Product. All rights are reserved.
4. FEEDBACK. If you inform Olive Tree of any errors, difficulties or other problems with the Product, or
make any suggestions as to changes or modifications to the Product (collectively, Feedback), Olive
Tree will have the right to use the Feedback for any purpose without compensation to you. All Feedback,
including any and all patents, copyrights, trade secrets and any and all other proprietary rights in or
derived from the Feedback, will be the sole property of Olive Tree.
5. NO DISTRIBUTION OR COMMERCIAL USE. You may not sell, resell, sublicense, rent, lease, lend, publish,
post, or otherwise provide or distribute the Product, in whole or in part, to any third party without the
express prior written consent of Olive Tree in each instance. You may not use or distribute the Product,
including but not limited to any content you create using the Product (e.g., personal notes, bookmarks,
reading schedules, etc.) for any commercial use or purpose.
6. RESTRICTED USE. You must use the Product in a manner consistent with all applicable laws and
regulations, and this EULA. You may not use the Product for any illegal, non-personal or unauthorized
purpose. You may not use the Product in a manner that could damage or cause risk to Olive Tree's business,
reputation, employees, customers, facilities, or to any third party. Unauthorized use of the Product
includes but is not limited to: (a) tampering with or using non-public areas of Olive Tree's website or
computer systems; (b) attempting to probe or test the vulnerability of Olive Tree's website or systems,
or to breach Olive Tree's security or authentication measures; (c) attempting to access or search the
Product, or Olive Tree's website or systems with any software or mechanism other than the software and/or
search agents provided by Olive Tree or other generally available third party browser; (d) attempting to
decompile, decipher, disassemble, reverse engineer or otherwise attempt to access or obtain the source
code of any of software comprising or in any way making up a part of Olive Tree's website or systems; or
(e) attempting to interfere with the access of any user, host or network, including but not limited to
sending a "virus" through the Product or Olive Tree's website or systems.
7. NO REVERSE ENGINEERING. You may not copy, list, print, publish, display, modify, create derivative
works of, translate, decompile, decipher, disassemble, reverse engineer or otherwise attempt to access or
obtain the source code of, or any other proprietary or confidential information from, the Product, in
whole or in part, except as expressly permitted by applicable law notwithstanding this limitation.
8. UPDATES. Olive Tree may, in its sole discretion, provide to you updates or supplements to the Product
("Updates"). If Olive Tree provides you any Updates, this EULA will apply to those Updates. The
Product may operate only on those hardware and software platforms specified in the Product documentation.
It is your responsibility to ensure that you have the appropriate software, hardware and Internet
connection to operate the then-current version of the Product. Olive Tree reserves the right to cease
supporting any hardware or software platform at any time, with or without notice.
9. USER ACCOUNT AND PASSWORD; SECURITY. You are entirely responsible for the security and confidentiality
of your password and account. Furthermore, you are entirely responsible for any and all activities that
occur under your account, including through the Product. You agree to immediately notify Olive Tree of
any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security of which you become aware.
10. TERMINATION; SUSPECTED BREACH. If you breach any of the terms and conditions of this EULA or Olive
Tree suspects any breach of this EULA, or for any other reason that affects Olive Tree's business,
customers or the public, Olive Tree may: (a) begin legal action, (b) immediately suspend or terminate the
EULA, or (c) cooperate with law enforcement in legal proceedings against violators. You agree to cooperate
with Olive Tree in investigating suspected violations. In the event of termination of this EULA, any and
all licenses granted to you under this EULA immediately cease, and you must: (i) immediately cease any use
of the Product and (ii) delete all copies of the Product in your possession, custody, or control,
including any copies of the Product on magnetic media or computer systems.
11. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES. THE PRODUCT AND ANY ACCOMPANYING SERVICES (E.G. DATA SYNCHRONIZATION)
ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "WITH ALL FAULTS" BASIS, AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS
OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, OR
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WHICH ARE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED. THERE IS NO WARRANTY THAT THE PRODUCT
WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, ALWAYS AVAILABLE, ACCURATE, COMPLETE, USEFUL, FUNCTIONAL OR ERROR FREE. THERE IS
NO WARRANTY THAT ANY DATA OR CONTENT YOU INPUT, IMPORT, TRANSFER, TRANSMIT, DOWNLOAD OR UPLOAD TO THE
PRODUCT OR ANY ACCOMPANYING WEBSITE WILL BE KEPT SECURELY. YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR USE
OF THE PRODUCT. ANY STATEMENTS MADE ON OR IN ANY PACKAGING, MANUALS, OR OTHER DOCUMENTS NOT EXPRESSLY
INCORPORATED HEREIN, AND ANY STATEMENTS MADE BY ANY OLIVE TREE EMPLOYEES OR REPRESENTATIVES, ARE PROVIDED
FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY AND NOT AS REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND BY OLIVE TREE. OLIVE
TREE DOES NOT AUTHORIZE ANYONE TO MAKE A WARRANTY OF ANY KIND ON OLIVE TREE'S BEHALF, AND YOU SHOULD NOT
RELY ON ANY SUCH STATEMENT. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE DISCLAIMER OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE
EXCLUSIONS IN THIS SECTION 11 MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, IN WHOLE OR IN PART.
12. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY; DISCLAIMER OF CERTAIN DAMAGES. EVEN IF OLIVE TREE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF
THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES, OLIVE TREE WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY DAMAGES
ARISING FROM THIS EULA OR USE OF THE PRODUCT OR ACCOMPANYING SERVICES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION:
PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, LOSS OF PRIVACY OR BREACH OF SECURITY
DAMAGES; PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGES; OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM INTERRUPTION OR
FAILURE OF THE PRODUCT, LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS DUE TO: (A) UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS
OR VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS, (B) THE INABILITY TO USE THE PRODUCT, OR (C) ANY INFORMATION,
CONTENT OR ANY FORM OF DATA THAT IS INPUT, IMPORTED, TRANSFERRED, TRANSMITTED TO, TRANSMITTED FROM,
RECEIVED FROM OR RECEIVED BY THE PRODUCT OR ANY ACCOMPANYING SERVICES. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE
EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR OTHER MODIFICATIONS OF OR LIMITATIONS
TO CERTAIN REMEDIES, SO THE EXCLUSIONS OR LIMITATIONS IN THIS SECTION 12 MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, IN WHOLE OR
IN PART.
THE MAXIMUM AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF OLIVE TREE TO YOU, AND THE EXCLUSIVE REMEDY AVAILABLE FOR ANY AND ALL
DAMAGES, INJURY, OR LOSSES ARISING FROM ANY AND ALL CLAIMS AND/OR CAUSES OF ACTION RELATED TO THE PRODUCT
OR THIS EULA WILL BE THE AMOUNT PAID BY YOU FOR THE APPLICABLE PRODUCT OR TEN DOLLARS ($10.00), WHICHEVER
IS THE GREATER. THE EXISTENCE OF MULTIPLE CLAIMS OR SUITS UNDER OR RELATED TO THIS EULA WILL NOT ENLARGE
OR EXTEND THE LIMITATION OF MONEY DAMAGES.
13. INDEMNIFICATION. You must defend, indemnify and hold Olive Tree harmless from and against any and all
claims, demands, actions, liabilities, costs or damages arising out of your use of the Product or your
violation of this EULA.
14. NO ASSIGNMENT. This EULA will be binding upon, inure to the benefit of, and be enforceable against
your respective successors and permitted assignees. You may not assign this EULA, or any of your rights,
interests, or obligations in connection with your use of the Product, without seeking and obtaining the
prior written consent of Olive Tree in each instance. Any such assignment without such consent will be
void and of no force and effect.
15. THIRD PARTY CONTENT. The Product may contain content or links to various third party web sites and
other resources ("Third Party Content"). This third party content (e.g. other than www.OliveTree.com)
is not under the control of Olive Tree and Olive Tree is not responsible or liable for the content,
communications or materials of any Third Party Content. Olive Tree, if applicable, provides this content
or links to you as a convenience only. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Olive Tree
of the Third Party Content or any association with its operators. You are responsible for adhering to the
applicable terms of service for any Third Party Content. You are solely responsible and liable for any
interactions you may have with such entities, their sponsors and other third parties.
16. U.S. GOVERNMENT LICENSE RIGHTS. All software provided to the U.S. Government pursuant to solicitations
issued on or after December 1, 1995 is provided with the commercial license rights and restrictions
described in this EULA. All software provided to the U.S. Government pursuant to solicitations issued
prior to December 1, 1995 is provided with "Restricted Rights" as provided for in FAR, 48 CFR 52.227-14
(JUNE 1987) or DFAR, 48 CFR 252.227-7013 (OCT 1988), as applicable.
17. EXPORT RESTRICTIONS. You acknowledge that the Product contains software that is subject to U.S.
export jurisdiction. You agree to comply with all applicable international and national laws that apply
to the Product, including the U.S. Export Administration Regulations, as well as end-user, end-use and
destination restrictions issued by U.S. and other governments. You hereby represent and warrant that (i)
you are not located in a country that is subject to a U.S. Government embargo, or that has been designated
by the U.S. Government as a 'terrorist supporting' country; and (ii) you are not listed on any U.S.
Government list of prohibited or restricted parties.
18. GOVERNING LAW; VENUE; ATTORNEYS' FEES. Washington state law governs the interpretation of this EULA
and applies to claims for breach of it, regardless of conflict of laws principles. The laws of the state
where you live govern all other claims, including claims under state consumer protection laws, unfair
competition laws, and in tort. Regardless of the choice of laws, any action arising out of or related to
this Agreement shall be brought in the state or federal courts located in Spokane, Washington, and each
party irrevocably consents to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of such courts. If either party employs
attorneys to enforce any rights arising out of or relating to this EULA, the prevailing party will be
entitled to recover its reasonable attorneys' fees, costs and other expenses.
19. ENTIRE AGREEMENT; NO WAIVER; SEVERABILITY. This EULA comprises the entire agreement and understanding
of you and Olive Tree regarding the Product and supersedes and replaces all other agreements or
representations, whether electronic, written or oral, regarding the subject matter of this EULA. Olive
Tree's failure at any time to require strict performance by you or any other licensees of any of the
provisions of this EULA does not waive Olive Tree's right to thereafter require strict compliance with
any provisions of this EULA. If a court of competent jurisdiction determines, in a final non-appealable
judgment, that any provision of this EULA is invalid, illegal, or otherwise unenforceable, such provision
will be deleted and the remainder of the EULA will be enforced as nearly as possible in accordance with
the stated intention of the parties. Electronic images of this EULA will be considered originals.
20. MODIFICATION OF THIS AGREEMENT. Olive Tree may modify this Agreement at any time in its sole
discretion. If so, a change of terms notice or a current version of this Agreement will be posted at the
Olive Tree website (at www.OliveTree.com). In the event of a material change to this Agreement we will
also use reasonable efforts to notify you by sending notice to the email address that you have provided to
us. If any modification is unacceptable to you, you agree that your only recourse is to immediately
terminate your use of the Product and destroy any installations of the Product on your devices and in
your possession. Your continued use of the Product following our posting of a change of terms notice or a
new end user licensing agreement on the Product will constitute your binding acceptance of the change.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS AGREEMENT INDICATES THAT YOU GIVE CONSENT TO OLIVE TREE TO SEND AN E-MAIL
COMMUNICATION TO YOU WITH NOTICES CONCERNING MATERIAL CHANGES IN THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT, THE
PRODUCT(S) OR OUR SERVICES TO WHICH YOU HAVE SUBSCRIBED.
21. CONTACT INFORMATION. If you have any questions regarding this EULA or the Product, you may contact us at:
Olive Tree Bible Software, Inc.
These Terms and Conditions of Use (the 'Terms Of Use') apply to the Olive Tree Bible Software ('Olive Tree')
web site located at <www.OliveTree.com>, and all associated sites by Olive Tree's subsidiaries and
affiliates, (collectively, the 'Site'). The Site is the property of Olive Tree.
BY USING THE SITE,
YOU AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF USE; IF YOU DO NOT AGREE, DO NOT USE THE SITE.
As long as you comply with these Terms Of Use, Olive Tree grants you a personal, non-exclusive,
non-transferable, limited privilege to enter, use the Site and view its content therein.
1. WEB SITE & SERVICES CONTENT.
All Olive Tree text, graphics, user interfaces, visual interfaces,
photographs, trademarks, logos, sounds, music, artwork and computer code (collectively, 'Content'),
including but not limited to the design, structure, selection, coordination, expression and arrangement
of such Content, contained on the Site is owned, controlled or licensed by or to Olive Tree.
Except as
expressly provided in these Terms Of Use, no part of the Site and no Content may be copied, reproduced,
republished, uploaded, posted, publicly displayed, encoded, translated, transmitted or distributed in any
way to any other computer, server, web site or other medium for publication or distribution or for any
commercial enterprise, without Olive Tree's express prior written consent.
2.
YOUR AUTHORIZED USES.
You may use information on the Site, as well as Olive Tree products and services
purposely made available by Olive Tree for downloading from the Site, provided that you: (a) not remove
any proprietary notice language in all copies of such documents, (b) use such information only for your
personal, non-commercial informational purpose and do not copy or post such information on any networked
computer or broadcast it in any media, (c) make no modifications to any such information, and (d) not make
any additional representations or warranties relating to such documents.
3.
PROHIBITED USES.
You may not use any scraper, robot, spider or other automated device, program,
algorithm or methodology, or any similar or equivalent manual process, to access, acquire, copy or monitor
any portion of the Site or any Content, or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure
or presentation of the Site or any Content, to obtain or attempt to obtain any materials, documents or
information through any means not purposely made available through the Site. Olive Tree reserves the right
to bar any such activity or access.
You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion or
feature of the Site, or any other systems or networks connected to the Site or to any Olive Tree server,
or to any of our services offered on or through the Site, by hacking, password mining or any other
illegitimate means.
You may not probe, scan or test the vulnerability of the Site or any network connected
to the Site, nor breach the security or authentication measures on the Site or any network connected to the
Site. You may not reverse look-up, trace or seek to trace any information on any other user of or visitor
to the Site, or any other customer of Olive Tree, including any Olive Tree account not owned by you, to its
source, or exploit the Site or any service or information made available or offered by or through the Site,
in any way where the purpose is to reveal any information, including but not limited to personal
identification or information, other than your own information, as provided for by the Site.
You agree
that you will not take any action that imposes an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on the
infrastructure of the Site or Olive Tree's systems or networks, or any systems or networks connected to
the Site or to Olive Tree.
You agree not to use any device, software or routine to interfere or attempt
to interfere with the proper working of the Site or any transaction being conducted on the Site, or with
any other person's use of the Site.
You may not forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in
order to disguise the origin of any message or transmittal you send to Olive Tree on or through the Site
or any service offered on or through the Site. You may not pretend that you are, or that you represent,
someone else, or impersonate any other individual or entity.
You may not use the Site or any Content for
any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms Of Use, or to solicit the performance of any
illegal activity or other activity which infringes the rights of Olive Tree or others.
4.
ACCOUNTS/IDENTIFICATION AND PASSWORDS.
Certain features or services offered on or through the Site may
require you to open an account (including setting up an Olive Tree account/identification and password).
You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the information you hold for your
account, including your password, and for any and all activity that occurs under your account as a result
of your failing to keep this information secure and confidential.
You agree to notify Olive Tree
immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or password, or any other breach of security.
You may
be held liable for losses incurred by Olive Tree or any other user of or visitor to the Site due to someone
else using your Olive Tree identification, password or account as a result of your failing to keep your
account information secure and confidential.
You may not use anyone else's Olive Tree identification,
password or account at any time without the express permission and consent of the holder of that Olive
Tree identification, password or account.
Olive Tree cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage
arising from your failure to comply with these obligations.
5.	TERMINATION; SUSPECTED BREACH.
If you breach any of these Terms Of Use or Olive Tree suspects any
breach of its privacy policy or end user license agreements, or for any other reason that affects Olive
Tree's business, customers or the public, Olive Tree may: (a) begin legal action, (b) immediately suspend
or terminate these Terms Of Use with you, or (c) cooperate with law enforcement in legal proceedings
against violators.
You agree that Olive Tree may, in its sole discretion and without prior notice,
terminate your access to the Site and/or block your future access to the Site if we determine that you
have violated these Terms Of Use or other agreements or guidelines which may be associated with your use
of the Site. You also agree that any violation by you of these Terms Of Use will constitute an unlawful
and unfair business practice, and will cause irreparable harm to Olive Tree, for which monetary damages
would be inadequate, and you consent to Olive Tree obtaining any injunctive or equitable relief that Olive
Tree deems necessary or appropriate in such circumstances.
These remedies are in addition to any other
remedies Olive Tree may have at law or in equity.
You agree to cooperate with Olive Tree in investigating
suspected violations.
In the event of termination of these Terms Of Use, any and all rights of use
granted to you under these Terms Of Use immediately cease, and you must immediately cease any use of the
Site.
6.	DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES.
OLIVE TREE DOES NOT PROMISE THAT THE SITE OR ANY CONTENT, SERVICE OR
FEATURE OF THE SITE WILL BE ERROR-FREE OR UNINTERRUPTED, OR THAT ANY DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT
YOUR USE OF THE SITE WILL PROVIDE SPECIFIC RESULTS. THE SITE AND ITS CONTENT ARE DELIVERED ON AN 'AS-IS'
AND 'AS-AVAILABLE' BASIS. ALL INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THE SITE IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE. OLIVE
TREE CANNOT ENSURE THAT ANY FILES OR OTHER DATA YOU DOWNLOAD FROM THE SITE WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES OR
CONTAMINATION OR DESTRUCTIVE FEATURES. OLIVE TREE DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING
ANY WARRANTIES OF ACCURACY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. OLIVE
TREE DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL LIABILITY FOR THE ACTS, OMISSIONS AND CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTIES IN
CONNECTION WITH OR RELATED TO YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND/OR ANY OLIVE TREE SERVICES. YOU ASSUME TOTAL
RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND ANY LINKED SITES. YOUR SOLE REMEDY AGAINST OLIVE TREE FOR
DISSATISFACTION WITH THE SITE OR ANY CONTENT IS TO STOP USING THE SITE OR ANY SUCH CONTENT. THIS
LIMITATION OF RELIEF IS A PART OF THE BARGAIN BETWEEN THE PARTIES.
The above disclaimer applies to any damages, liability or injuries caused by any failure of performance,
error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus,
communication line failure, theft or destruction of or unauthorized access to, alteration of, or use,
whether for breach of contract, tort, negligence or any other cause of action.
Olive Tree reserves the
right to do any of the following, at any time, without notice: (1) to modify, suspend or terminate
operation of or access to the Site, or any portion of the Site, for any reason; (2) to modify or change
the Site, or any portion of the Site, and any applicable policies or terms; and (3) to interrupt the
operation of the Site, or any portion of the Site, as necessary to perform routine or non-routine
maintenance, error correction, or other changes.
IF YOU ARE UTILIZING ANY SERVICES OFFERED BY OLIVE TREE THROUGH THIS WEBSITE (E.G. DATA SYNCHRONIZATION),
SUCH SERVICES ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "WITH ALL FAULTS" BASIS, AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND,
EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY,
NON-INFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WHICH ARE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED.
THERE IS NO
WARRANTY THAT OUR SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, ALWAYS AVAILABLE, ACCURATE, COMPLETE, USEFUL, FUNCTIONAL
OR ERROR FREE.
THERE IS NO WARRANTY THAT ANY DATA OR CONTENT YOU INPUT, IMPORT, TRANSFER, TRANSMIT,
DOWNLOAD OR UPLOAD TO THE PRODUCT OR ANY ACCOMPANYING WEBSITE WILL BE KEPT SECURELY.
OLIVE TREE DOES NOT
AUTHORIZE ANYONE TO MAKE A WARRANTY OF ANY KIND ON OLIVE TREE'S BEHALF, AND YOU SHOULD NOT RELY ON ANY
SUCH STATEMENT.
SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE DISCLAIMER OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE EXCLUSIONS IN THIS
SECTION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, IN WHOLE OR IN PART.
7.	LIMITATION OF LIABILITY; DISCLAIMER OF CERTAIN DAMAGES.
EVEN IF OLIVE TREE HAS BEEN ADVISED
OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES, OLIVE TREE WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY DAMAGES
ARISING FROM THESE TERMS OF USE OR USE OF OLIVE TREE SERVICES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION: PUNITIVE,
EXEMPLARY, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, LOSS OF PRIVACY OR BREACH OF SECURITY DAMAGES;
PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGES; OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM INTERRUPTION OR FAILURE OF
THE PRODUCT, LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS DUE TO: (A) UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS OR VIRUSES
OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS, (B) THE INABILITY TO USE THE WEB SITE OR SERVICES, OR (C) ANY INFORMATION,
CONTENT OR ANY FORM OF DATA THAT IS INPUT, IMPORTED, TRANSFERRED, TRANSMITTED TO, TRANSMITTED FROM,
RECEIVED FROM OR RECEIVED BY THE PRODUCT OR ANY ACCOMPANYING SERVICES.
SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE
EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR OTHER MODIFICATIONS OF OR LIMITATIONS
TO CERTAIN REMEDIES, SO THE EXCLUSIONS OR LIMITATIONS IN THIS SECTION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, IN WHOLE OR IN
PART.
THE MAXIMUM AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF OLIVE TREE TO YOU, AND THE EXCLUSIVE REMEDY AVAILABLE FOR ANY AND ALL
DAMAGES, INJURY, OR LOSSES ARISING FROM ANY AND ALL CLAIMS AND/OR CAUSES OF ACTION RELATED TO THE SITE,
OLIVE TREE SERVICES OR THESE TERMS OF USE, IN COMBINATION WITH ANY OTHER AGREEMENTS ENTERED INTO WITH
OLIVE TREE (E.G. END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT), WILL BE THE AMOUNT PAID BY YOU FOR AN APPLICABLE OLIVE TREE
PRODUCT OR SERVICE, OR TEN DOLLARS ($10.00), WHICHEVER IS THE GREATER.
THE EXISTENCE OF MULTIPLE CLAIMS
OR SUITS UNDER OR RELATED TO THESE TERMS OF USE WILL NOT ENLARGE OR EXTEND THE LIMITATION OF MONEY DAMAGES.
8.	INDEMNIFICATION.
You must defend, indemnify and hold Olive Tree harmless from and against any and all
claims, demands, actions, liabilities, costs or damages arising out of your use of the Site or your
violation of these Terms Of Use.
9.	NO ASSIGNMENT.
These Terms Of Use will be binding upon, inure to the benefit of, and be enforceable
against your respective successors and permitted assignees.
You may not assign these Terms Of Use, or
any of your rights, interests, or obligations in connection with your use of the Site, without seeking and
obtaining the prior written consent of Olive Tree in each instance.
Any such assignment without such
consent will be void and of no force and effect.
10. THIRD PARTY CONTENT.
The Site may contain content or links to various third party web sites and other
resources ("Third Party Content"). This Third Party Content (e.g. other than www.OliveTree.com) is
not under the control of Olive Tree and Olive Tree is not responsible or liable for the content,
communications or materials of any Third Party Content. Olive Tree, if applicable, provides this content
or links to you as a convenience only.
The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Olive Tree
of the Third Party Content or any association with its operators.
You are responsible for adhering to the
applicable terms of use for any Third Party Content. You are solely responsible and liable for any
interactions you may have with such entities, their sponsors and other third parties.
On some rare
circumstances, it may be necessary ? by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and
governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence ? for Olive Tree to disclose your
personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of
national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or
appropriate.
We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably
necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the
event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to
the relevant third party.
11.	EXPORT RESTRICTIONS.
You may not use or export or re-export any Content or any copy or adaptation
of such Content, or any product or service offered on the Site, in violation of any applicable laws or
regulations, including without limitation United States export laws and regulations.
12.	GOVERNING LAW; VENUE; ATTORNEYS' FEES.
Washington state law governs the interpretation of these
Terms Of Use and applies to claims for breach of it, regardless of conflict of laws principles.
The laws
of the state where you live govern all other claims, including claims under state consumer protection laws,
unfair competition laws, and in tort.
Regardless of the choice of laws, any action arising out of or
related to this Agreement shall be brought in the state or federal courts located in Spokane, Washington,
and each party irrevocably consents to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of such courts.
If either
party employs attorneys to enforce any rights arising out of or relating to these Terms Of Use, the
prevailing party will be entitled to recover its reasonable attorneys' fees, costs and other expenses.
13.	ENTIRE AGREEMENT; NO WAIVER; SEVERABILITY.
These Terms of Use comprise the entire agreement and
understanding of you and Olive Tree regarding the Olive Tree web site and related services, and supersedes
and replaces all other agreements or representations, whether electronic, written or oral, regarding the
subject matter of this agreement.
Olive Tree's failure at any time to require strict performance by you
or any other licensees of any of the provisions of this agreement does not waive Olive Tree's right to
thereafter require strict compliance with any provisions of this agreement.
If a court of competent
jurisdiction determines, in a final non-appealable judgment, that any provision of this agreement is
invalid, illegal, or otherwise unenforceable, such provision will be deleted and the remainder of the
agreement will be enforced as nearly as possible in accordance with the stated intention of the parties.
Electronic images of this agreement will be considered originals.
14.	MODIFICATION OF THIS AGREEMENT.
As summarily noted above, Olive Tree may modify these Terms Of Use
at any time in its sole discretion.
If so, a change of terms notice or a current version of this Agreement
will be posted at the Olive Tree website (at www.OliveTree.com).
In the event of a material change to
this Agreement we will also use reasonable efforts to notify you by sending notice to the email address
that you have provided to us.
If any modification is unacceptable to you, you agree that your only
recourse is to immediately terminate your use of the Site and related services.
Your continued use of
the Site and related services following our posting of a change of terms notice will constitute your
binding acceptance of the change.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS AGREEMENT INDICATES THAT YOU GIVE CONSENT TO
OLIVE TREE TO SEND AN E-MAIL COMMUNICATION TO YOU WITH NOTICES CONCERNING MATERIAL CHANGES IN THE TERMS
OF THIS AGREEMENT, THE PRODUCT(S) OR OUR SERVICES TO WHICH YOU HAVE SUBSCRIBED.
15. PRIVACY POLICY & END USER LICENSE . Olive Tree's Privacy Policy applies to use of this Site, and its
terms are made a part of these Terms Of Use by this reference. To view Olive Tree's Privacy Policy,
review our Privacy Policy . Additionally, if you utilize any of Olive Tree's
software, then it is highly recommended that
you review our End User's License Agreement, which shall take precedence over any
conflict of terms that may be referenced herein.
16.	CONTACT INFORMATION.
If you have any questions regarding these Terms Of Use, or any related services
or software, you may contact us at:
Olive Tree Bible Software, Inc.
We want our users to have the best experience possible with Olive Tree products. We realize that, on
occasion, a product may not meet your expectations, therefore we can consider requests for refunds made
within 30 days of the purchase of that item on OliveTree.com. We apologize, but we are not able to provide
refunds on purchases made within app stores such as iTunes, as those purchases are subject to the terms and
conditions that you agreed to when you set up your account with them. In certain cases we may be
prohibited from providing a refund due to publisher restrictions; please see product descriptions for
details about individual product eligibility.
